Visit turkision.com for more!
What are you saying, Yakup Bey?
Yakup Bey!
What are you doing?
You let my prey escape!
Today...
you are the prey.
And I am the hunter, Osman!
Isn't there news from Vasilis?
He still hasn't left the border market,
Master.
Yakup is taking precaution.
The old wolf thinks of all possibilities.
Well, what are you thinking of doing?
We'll take Vasilis out of there.
Let him come...
You planned a real good game,
right, Crusader?
Now Yakup and Osman
are against one another.
They'll drown in their own blood.
But...
I don't trust the game...
I trust my sword.
Send word to the soldiers
to surround the Inn!
After you...
I will kill that dog too.
It's not about getting rid of
the enemy.
Rather the traitor among us...
we must get rid of them!
Yakup Bey!
You're testing my patience.
But I can't hold it back anymore.
Your betrayal...
has been exposed, Osman.
You will answer now.
You will die!
I have nothing to answer to you for...
nor do I owe you my life!
I waited until now for peace.
But now it's over.
Today, only one of us will leave here alive.
Let's see who that will be...
Yakup Bey!
You knew the punishment for betrayal.
You did this knowingly.
Now it's time to pay the price!
I said you wouldn't open your eyes
before falling into negligence.
But it seems you won't open
your eyes before dying.
Tell me.
With whose words did you come here?
With which dog's words?
Your Alp, Veysel!
Veysel?
Veysel is the traitor in my palace.
Bayındır was after him.
Do you came and face me
with the words of a traitor?
We have been dealing with
them for so long.
You couldn't walk the path even a little.
Do you still fall for their games?
We didn't learn the game from
infidels like you did, Osman.
They came before us,
and we crushed them.
But you learnt to betray from them.
What's your proof?
The Mongol poison was
brought from your palace.
The poison that poisoned
my daughter Gonca.
They plot their games in such a way...
it's impossible not to believe it.
There's no game.
I was always right, Osman.
They always was a game.
But you were always wrong.
Alps!
Leave the Germiyans!
Turn to the heathens!
Alps! Kill the Mongols!
You're going to ruin my meticulously
planned game with this attack!
The game is yours.
The war is ours, crusader.
While they're both inside,
I won't stand still.
You will be the cause of them uniting!
Let that scare you, crusader.
I...
am the servant of Olcaytu Han,
and soldier of Emir Çoban.
I am the link that holds their state
together with taxes.
Together or separate, it makes no difference.
I am their executioner.
If they were to go down fighting,
we would have made them fall.
You will be in need of my games...
Mongols.
Master, everything was done
as you commanded.
Our men are waiting at the border market.
Good.
Let's go.
There's nothing left to do here.
Hold the entrances.
My Bey, these dogs keep coming.
You leave. I'll come after you.
Be careful, son.
- Be careful.
- Don't worry, my Bey.
Konur.
We'll leave from the back door.
Yakup Bey.
Come on.
Come on, son.
The dog that shows its teeth to the wolf...
ends up dead.
Alps.
Release the doors.
Your teeth can't do anything to me.
But I will ruin you all.
GERMIYANOĞLU BORDER / BORDER MARKET
Take this. Eat. You shouldn't die.
Give me.
It's time for you to get out of the cage.
Jesus' loyal soldiers are coming for you.
Get ready.
Master.
Saadet Hatun!
Yakup Bey!
Come outside!
Saadet Hatun!
Who am I talking to?
Get out of my way!
Ülgen, where is my son?
Bala Hatun.
Your son is in the prison, Bala.
Until Yakup Bey comes...
he is under arrest.
Saadet Hatun.
I want my son and my Alps.
You probably didn't hear me.
Until Yakup Bey comes...
they are all under arrest.
For what reason?
What is their crime?
You will find out when Yakup Bey comes.
Saadet Hatun, your scales of justice
have lost balance.
Alaeddin has committed no crime.
I will not allow you to imprison
my son for no reason.
Alps!
This is my land.
Just as I was your guest
in your palace...
now your son and your Alps
are my guests.
You want reprisal, huh?
Not at all.
My intention is very sincere.
Your son and your Alps...
are my guests...
until Yakup Bey comes.
Since you say your intention is sincere...
then release my Alps.
You have no problem with them.
I will be the better person.
Your Alps are free.
Now, Bala Hatun...
go.
No.
Until my son is released...
I will stay right here, Saadet Hatun.
You won't stand still, Bala.
I know.
But...
leave my market now.
I won't go anywhere without taking my son.
Since this is your land...
...what are you afraid of?
Then you will stay...
and your Alps will go
Alps, be careful.
These Mongols aren't like the others.
We are suffering because
of your mistakes.
You brought the Mongols upon us
before we could even get on our feet.
What you call a mistake is the fire
of the independence of the Turks.
Yes, I brought them upon us...
but I didn't give them a good time.
Osman.
Alps!
There's no escape from my might.
You will feel my wrath now!
You bring your wrath on the oppressed.
But we are the protectors
of the oppressed.
And our wrath will fall on all
the oppressors!
You'll see.
Come on, Boran!
- Allah is the Greatest!
- O Right!
Ya Allah!
I will rain death upon you!
Today, these lands will
be your graves!
Bala Hatun.
Bayındır Bey and the Alps are now free.
Okay. Good.
Why is this cart in a hurry?
Where is it going?
Hasan...
take some Alps with you and
go after it quickly. Come on.
As you command, Bala Hatun.
Veysel!
How did you hide yourself for so long?
How couldn't I see it?
Gonca Hatun. Gonca Hatun.
Gonca Hatun.
Mehmet Bey has strict orders...
we cannot let anyone in.
Am I anyone?
Get out.
Oh, welcome, deceitful Hatun.
Don't look at me like that.
I thought your father wouldn't believe it?
What were you going to do by raiding
my father's tent, Alaeddin Bey ?
My father would've heard
Veysel out either way.
I don't understand, Gonca.
He trusts the word of one man.
Is there someone else?
Osman Bey will go to
someone named Karacelasun.
Their numbers are small.
Alaeddin was going to chart the path.
I don't know.
Does it hurt?
Do you feel guilty?
Or do you pity me?
Why would I feel guilty?
I don't know.
Maybe because your brother did this to me.
I got my answer.
What's the answer?
You couldn't harm me.
Is that so?
Your tongue has no limits.
If you talk like that again,
you'll see how I hurt you.
You're not only deceitful...
you're also heartless.
Heartless Gonca.
Your father believed Veysel.
What about you?
Do you believe him?
I believe you.
And when my father speaks to Osman Bey...
he will surely understand the truth.
Do you...
really trust me?
I do.
Do you trust me?
Gonca?
Allah is the Greatest!
Ya Allah!
Boran Bey...
what will we do when
our arrows run out?
My Bey, all our arrows have run out.
We will wait.
They can't resist.
They have no strength to resist.
Strike them, soldiers of Erlik Han!
Stand together!
Alps! Shoot your arrows!
Son?
Allah is the Greatest!
Soldiers, retreat!
I won't die before getting my revenge.
The wrath of the dark spirits
will fall upon you!
Come on!
- Ya Allah!
Are you in love with Alaeddin?
I'm asking you.
I gave you a duty, but...
Mother, what are you saying?
You heard me.
If I loved Alaeddin...
would I tell you what I heard?
Would I do such a thing?
Don't you know me, Mother?
How would I know?
It's love.
One cannot know.
Right? Gonca.
You've defended the Kayıs many times.
When Alaeddin was arrested,
you stood in your brother's way.
Mother.
I always said what
I believed to be right.
What does this have
to do with Alaeddin?
Don't disappoint me, Gonca.
If you love Alaeddin...
this will only burden you,
my daughter.
You can go now.
Don't forget.
Alaeddin is only your duty.
Fitnat.
Tell Gülce...
she will watch Gonca's every move
and inform me.
- Do you understand?
- I understand, Saadet Hatun.
Oh, Gonca.
Your eyes and your heart differ,
my daughter.
How did Mehmet Bey save you
in the raid? He is very brave.
He values you obviously.
What was Orhan Bey doing then?
He was busy saving Aysima.
Have you really forgiven him?
No.
I haven't forgiven him,
I can't forgive him.
I really want to forgive him.
But that picture doesn't leave my mind.
Have a good day, Holofira.
You said you didn't want it, but I thought
you'd change your mind on seeing the horse.
You are very thoughful.
It seems to be a thoroughbred horse
Will you accept it?
I probably behaved brash yesterday.
I owe you my life and I couldn't thank you.
If you accept the horse,
that will be your thanks.
Refusing would be rude of me.
Thank you.
You made me very happy, Holofira.
You should know, seeing you
like this makes me feel better.
Always smile.
Thank you.
I will go now.
Holofira. What have you done?
When my brother hears about this,
all Hell will break loose.
Where are the Alps, Gökmen?
Didn't I tell you that this tent
won't be left unguarded?
- My Prince...
- Be quiet!
Be quiet!
Veysel!
Gather your Alps quickly, Gökmen.
Quickly!
Alps!
Bala Hatun.
What is the reason we sent
Hasan Alp after that cart?
The cart left the market
in a hurry.
Clearly something is up.
They shouldn't leave the cart.
They should find out who is inside.
Our concern now is Alaeddin.
Alright.
My Bey, there are traces up to the water,
then they disappear. They are unclear.
My Sultan, there's no trace. It's as if
they put on wings and flew away.
We lost that baseborn dog!
Who knows where he'll hide
and when he'll attack!
This is because of you, Yakup Bey!
You raided the Inn. You let
those who harmed us escape.
They said that Osman was
the one who hurt my daughter.
What should I have done?
My daughter's life was at risk.
I wasn't going to just sit in my tent.
Whoever said so is more of a
dog than those that escaped!
Now we will return to the border market.
If we trusted your words and came,
we don't trust you enough to let you go.
You will face Veysel.
We will see who's a traitor and who isn't.
Let's go, Yakup Bey.
Let's definitely go.
But if you fall into negligence and one of
the Mongols hurt someone in my family...
you will pay dearly for this.
Just so you know.
You think about the answer you'll give first.
Then hold us accountable.
Come on.
You can't even hold one man.
And you?
The man runs away in front of your
eyes you and you don't even realise.
Gökmen, you embarrassed me.
It's time for you to fix your mistake.
- Don't come back until you find that man.
- As you command, my Prince.
You will be punished for this failure.
Get out of my sight now.
- Get lost!
- Alps! Let's go!
What happened, Mehmet?
What is this state of the Alps, brother?
Or...
They took Veysel, Osman's Alp.
How did they do this with all
these Alps around, Mehmet?
Or was it Bala?
No.
We took precautions for the Kayı Alps.
Gülce is watching Bala Hatun,
she couldn't do this.
It's my fault, mother.
I couldn't place strict measures.
But I will find that dog wherever he goes.
Maybe that Veysel is a traitor
as Alaeddin Bey said?
Of course, he ran away when he
realised we'd find out about him.
- Gonca!
Stop, driver! I said stop!
Alps, be careful.
You dog!
Where will you run to?
Keep going.
You foolish Turks, you will never beat us.
We'll always find a way out.
We will start, Lord Vasilis.
Alps!
The cloths were loaded onto the cart.
They're waiting for us, Lord Vasilis.
You'll get on the cart quickly.
Vasilis.
My friend.
I knew you wouldn't leave me.
I would burn all the border lands
and take you from there.
I know you would, Master Gera.
And I would have burned myself
for the cause if you asked...
Never.
I would never sacrifice you.
Your absence will make them crazy.
Osman and Yakup will vent
their anger on each other.
I already lit the fire between them.
Yakup arrested Alaeddin and Bayındır
thanks to the strife I caused.
He will detain them and
never release them.
The old wolf will keep
them in place of you.
I'm starting to get curious
about my next task from now.
Osman will not stop before he proves
you are a traitor and saves his son.
He won't stop following you.
Your new task is to never get caught.
Hide in a safe place and
wait for news from me.
What about you, Master Gera?
What's on your mind?
I am a trader.
Master Gera.
Karacelasun is returning with his soldiers.
- Osman and Yakup are...
- Alive!
That big-headed Mongol!
If it was possible to defeat without
tricks, we would have done it.
The Mongols will learn this too!
Let's go and meet the Mongols before Yakup.
Let's explain to him why he couldn't kill him.
Vasilis.
Don't get caught.
Wait for news from me.
Come on.
Let's go.
Sultan Yakup is coming.
Osman Bey is coming.
Osman?
Why is he still alive now, mother?
Your father must know something.
Don't question him, Mehmet.
Worry about your own mistake.
Praise be to Allah.
Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you.
It seems Yakup Bey wasn't the only
one who believed the slander.
But all the people believed this slander.
While we were about to defeat that dog that
raided the market and caused us pain...
Yakup Bey came and
let him escape.
Now bring that dog who slandered me.
Bring Veysel!
Veysel escaped, my Bey.
Did you do this so that he doesn't
speak the truth, Osman?
Did you smuggle Veysel?
You stand in front of me
with the word of a dog...
we fight with you, back to back,
because you are one of us...
and now you're trying to hold
us accountable for your failure.
Watch your words, Osman Bey.
Watch it so you can live long.
Likewise, Yakup Bey.
Let there be an to your slanders.
You keep saying it's slander but...
Bala Hatun has been in the
market for a long time.
She says she wants Alaeddin, but it seems
there were other people she wanted.
If you detain my son and
accuse me at the same time...
it changes everything,
white becomes red, Saadet Hatun.
Bala.
Is Alaeddin a prisoner in your hands?
I hold the whole world captive until the
matter becomes clear, if necessary.
Who is Alaeddin, Osman Bey?
I will make the world Hell for the
one who imprisons Alaeddin.
Don't hesitate.
Whoever hesitates hurts me.
Go first, Mehmet Bey.
Alps!
Close all entrances and
exits to the market.
Veysel is one of the Crusaders.
Clearly there is a traitor inside.
They allowed him to escape.
There can be no traitor on my land.
Do you want the truth or
do you want problems?
They believed in victory.
They fell into ambushes.
We ripped the courage
out of their hearts.
And now we will take their lives.
I told you.
If you had listened to me,
you wouldn't have been wounded.
Crusader.
We live to fight.
Our wounds are our path.
Our path is known, Mongols.
Yakup captured Osman's son.
My game is ready.
Think.
So far, we have set Yakup upon Osman.
But what did Osman do?
He was not defeated by his pride.
He assumed humility.
He did not fight Yakup.
Yakup is not like Osman.
Not at all.
He is arrogant and ambitious.
When Osman walks towards Yakup...
Yakup will be defeated by his
pride, he will not assume humility.
He will fall for the game and enter into war.
Karacelasun.
Osman's son, Alaeddin...
His intelligent and most valuable one.
We will kill him.
We will put the blame on Yakup.
I like your game, Crusader.
You do that and I'll do my part.
Great Mergen.
Listen to Erlik Han.
I hear Erlik Han.
He sends them death.
So, you're the traitor? Come on!
Come here!
Come on!
Kneel!
My Bey, this is the traitor.
Dağhan Alp.
Don't slander, Orhan.
The one who infiltrated my palace...
will he hesitate to enter your market,
Mehmet?
Until Veysel is found...
this dog will continue to breathe.
They bring the poison of the Mongols
with the hands of the Crusaders.
It is clear that they have allied.
We will find out who they are.
That's why...
this dog will live until then.
Look at me.
You will release Alaeddin.
I will find that Veysel and I will bring
him and throw him before your eyes.
Let it be my promise.
Kanyumaz.
Alaeddin is alive.
He is fine.
Until Veysel is found...
he will be my guest.
Yakup Bey.
Look.
I am striving to improve the situation.
But you...
you are ruining everything.
While I'm trying not to spill blood...
you are forcing the blood to be spilled.
If my son is not released...
I will be the first to shed blood, enough!
Perhaps your blood will be spilled first, Bala.
- Mother.
- Son?
Father.
Alaeddin.
Brother.
Veysel's betrayal is clear.
He will be found.
We have no fear.
Since Yakup Bey has doubts...
and wants leverage...
I have no objection in being his guest,
my Bey.
No. No.
Mother.
There's no problem.
Yakup Bey will host me well.
Don't be upset.
We found one traitor...
we will find the other one too.
But, Yakup Bey, until then...
if a hair on my son's head is hurt...
this market...
and this tent, I will bring it down
over your head, just so you know.
For your own betterment...
I'll assume I didn't hear these words,
Osman Bey.
You have two days.
Bring Veysel...
and take Alaeddin.
Otherwise this is hosting...
will turn into a difficult captivity.
When the truth comes out...
how will you pay for this slander?
There are many prices to be paid,
Osman Bey.
Two days.
Go on.
Have a safe journey.
Alps!
Bala Hatun.
Allow me to come with you.
Come, my daughter, come.
Brother.
Holofira is going home.
She left with her new horse a while ago.
What horse, sister?
What are you saying?
Mehmet Bey gifted her a horse.
And Holofira accepted it.
I never expected her to accept it.
So she accepted it?
I shouldn't have said this.
I hope from Allah that this tongue of mine...
Holofira.
The dark spirits will drag them to death.
Their end will come soon.
My soldiers!
My revenge...
will become a legend...
and reach the other world.
But...
first, we need soldiers for this.
We...
are enough for them,
Commander Karacelasun.
No. No.
The more we are...
the less our blood will be spilled.
Every drop...
of my soldiers' blood...
is a gift from Erlik Han.
We will live...
and they will die!
Mergen.
Tomorrow you will quickly go to Tabriz.
Soldiers there who are waiting to die...
you'll bring them with you.
- As you command, Commander Karacelasun.
- Go on.
When the soldiers come...
I will feed Osman's head to the dogs.
In Sha Allah.
(If Allah permits)
- In Sha Allah.
In Sha Allah, Karacelasun.
Well then, trader Ayhan Ağa...
should go to the border market.
Let us talk a little with Yakup Bey.
While we talk...
let your heroes strike the neck of Osman's
son Alaeddin whose mind is valuable.
Then what will Osman Bey do?
He will have lost his son.
He will take revenge...
for his valuable Alaeddin Bey.
In order to avenge his son...
he will attack Yakup Bey.
Then, Alaeddin's...
head full of knowledge...
I will gift it to your soldiers.
I make things easier for your soldiers.
Victory is one...
and the enemy is one, Crusader.
We'll talk.
Come on.
What do you want?
You liked the gift very much,
didn't you?
It seems word spreads very fast
in these border lands.
Holofira, how could you...
how could you accept Mehmet's gift?
Do you expect me to answer to you?
Who are you, Orhan?
Who are you to me?
- I am your...
- What are you to me?
Who are you to me, Orhan?
You can't say it, but I'll say it.
You are no one to me.
You cannot interfere in my matters.
If you want to interfere so much,
go and interfere with your sister Fatma.
Or in fact...
what was her name? Aysima...
go and interfere in her matters
if you so badly want to.
In any case, she's inside the palace
next to your mother, isn't it?
That gift you took from Mehmet...
you'll give it back, Holofira.
Maybe she made you sweetmeat again.
You liked it very much.
Go and eat it.
Aysima...
is no one to me.
Is that why you saved her life?
So...
the freedom of my prince...
depends on what you say, is it?
Look at me,
you will speak.
You will speak.
- Wait.
- That's more like it.
Veysel...
his real name...
is Vasilis.
He is above us.
Keep talking, go on.
I will speak because...
we...
will kill all of you.
What is this disgrace?
Mehmet?
You lost the man in your hand.
And the Alp under your command...
turns out a traitor.
While everything is mixed up...
don't pressure Mehmet.
Should it have been...
Osman's Alps who found the tracks, Hatun?
Even the traitor among us...
should they have discovered it?
And while we say that our son...
is brave...
and crafty...
There will never be such weakness again.
Let there not be, Mehmet.
Let there not be.
I will not accept mistakes anymore.
Keep the Alps alert.
And let's be ready when Cerkutay brings
information from Osman's palace.
As you command, my Bey.
- May I come in, my Sultan?
- Come in.
My Sultan, Ayhan Ağa has come.
He would like to see you.
Let him wait.
My prince is coming.
My brother is a prisoner there, couldn't
you make this traitor is speak, valiants?
My prince.
Baysungur said to cut his tongue...
we didn't want to lose hope,
we waited for you.
You need not lose hope
and cut his tongue.
While there are many places
which can be cut...
Aykurt.
This man is a warrior. He's
not afraid of beatings or death.
But...
But which way you die matters.
My brother taught me.
If I cut his neck from here, the blood
will flow fast and he will die quickly.
But that doesn't work for me.
But if I cut from here...
the blood will flow from his mouth and nose...
and in his own blood...
he will drown.
As long as you don't speak, my
brother will remain captive there.
If something happens to
him while he's there...
I will cut you into pieces...
and bury your pieces everywhere.
Alps!
Hang him from his feet and start cutting.
Let his blood flow inside it so
our land does not get dirty.
And if he speaks, tell me.
Okay, my prince.
Alps, let's hang this dog.
It bothers me to leave Alaeddin
there like this, Osman.
Bala is right, they can't be trusted.
Don't worry, Yakup Bey can't do anything.
He wouldn't dare do something like that.
Let's go now...
let's go and find this dog.
- My Bey.
- Son, come.
My Bey, how do you think
they got him out?
The market can be easily infiltrated by cart.
The Mongols have done the same.
And then they can leave
with the cart too.
When we were in the market,
a cart left in a hurry.
I sent Hasan after it.
If he's in the cart, we'll find him soon.
Well thought, Bala.
Well thought.
But we will never give
the enemy a chance.
We will always go after the clues.
They don't think about Alaeddin or Veysel.
While we were happy because
Mongols were becoming Muslim...
but one shaman appeared and
ruined everything.
As if that wasn't enough, they
united with the Crusaders.
If they unite, we will unite too.
Tell me, who has taken Candar Bey's place?
His son, Süleyman Bey. He was chosen
by majority vote in the council, my Bey.
We went to these Beys and saved them...
and we gained a great reputation.
But we have not used this reputation yet.
Now...
send messengers to the Beys.
The Beys we called for war, let them come.
Let them come to our court
and sit at our table.
Because we must unite as well.
My Bey, what is your
goal with this move?
We withdrew our pledge and
made our move.
Now I am curious about their loyalty.
When I say I will lead...
I will see who will stand behind me
and who will stand against me.
- May I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
GERMIYANOĞLU BORDER / BORDER MARKET
Everything that befalls us
benefits Osman.
He is always looking for our weaknesses.
It's enough, mother, I'll solve this.
Of course you will solve it.
But first you will take care of Holofira.
She is on my mind, mother.
I take hold of her slowly.
She accepted the horse I gave her today.
Her temperament was very good.
Don't go slowly, my lion.
It's time to hurry.
Tell Holofira of your intention tomorrow.
Tell her you want to marry her.
As you wish, mother.
My Sultan...
I know, I'm disturbing you, but...
the recent unfortunate events...
you know about it.
These things happen all the time.
We didn't come to know the Mongols yesterday,
Ayhan Ağa.
It certainly is
But...
the customers, the source of our blessing...
they fear for their lives, my Sultan.
They no longer come to the market, and
when they don't come, our profits decline.
Well, you kept saying you're a good trader.
If you didn't have a solution,
you wouldn't come to meet me.
My Sultan, I don't have a solution.
But I have great concerns.
Tell me without stalling, Ayhan Ağa.
The Mongols, my sultan.
I mean, those murderers...
these barbarians, if they
want to kill everyone...
they would do it...
with pleasure.
They raid and they leave halfway.
Then...
I mean, the traitors...
walk out of here freely.
Now, my Sultan, these incidents break trust.
- Trust...
- What does that mean, Ayhan Ağa?
Are these all games?
Mehmet Bey.
I don't want to say, but...
what I think is...
one of they Beys amongst you...
agrees with them.
And creates a new market,
that's what I understand.
What do you know, Ayhan Ağa?
The time has come, my brothers.
Alaeddin will die tonight, let's get started.
My Bey, what Orhan Bey did worked.
The dog told us about the place.
It is a place near the Karapınar region.
My Bey, let me quickly go and get him.
No, stop, son.
We will wait.
My Bey, forgive me, but
I agree with the prince.
If Hasan comes and tells us another place,
let's raid that place too.
Our time is tight, and
we have no time to wait.
My Bey must know something.
Of course. Osman Bey would
like to be sure first.
If the place the traitor told us...
is different from the place Hasan tells us...
one of them will be a trap.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, I watched the cart up
to the Karapınar region.
Some of them clashed with me
then the cart disappeared from sight.
I saw him, my Bey.
Veysel was inside it.
My Bey.
The place Hasan tells us about
is the same as what the traitor said.
Veysel is there, my Bey.
Let's go and get him and come back.
Didn't you say that Veysel has a
high position among the Crusaders?
These people will not tell who their
superior is even when they're dying.
They also cut off Hasan's path.
They know very well that
we are after them.
My Bey.
Do you mean the traitor is
taking us into a trap?
Exactly that, he is setting a trap for us.
But don't forget, son...
if we know where the trap is,
we'll be setting the real trap.
Veysel sets a trap for us.
We said Crusaders are cooperating
with the Mongols, my Bey.
Will it be just be Veysel?
Brother, is that dog Karacelasun also there?
Everyone wants this, they want to destroy us.
Let them come, whatever the outcome...
we'll take Veysel.
There will be many dogs.
Get ready.
As my Bey commands.
We'll take that dog first...
and then my brother.
I won't differentiate between any of them.
Bala, prepare the yard
while we make our move.
When the Beys enter, they
will see our prestige.
Don't worry, my Bey. When the
great Turk Beys enter the palace...
they will see what prestige is.
Thank you.
Malhun.
Go to the border market,
don't let them out of your sight.
My eyes will be on Germiyan, my Bey.
Thank you.
We will make our move
and heads will fall.
After that there will be war,
then there'll be weddings.
- In Sha Allah.
In Sha Allah, my Bey.
In fact, I wanted to leave you hungry, but...
I can't hurt you.
There's a trap.
Alaeddin.
Alps!
Yakup Bey has ordered,
you will die tonight, Alaeddin.
Only Allah knows this.
Bala?
Bala.
Alaeddin...
Sit down, are you okay?
I have a bad feeling in my heart.
Don't.
We will stand strong, we will not give up.
Don't worry.
I will save my son from their hands.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Are you?
- I'm fine, it's nothing.
Since you doubt the
establishment of a market...
tell me completely now,
what do you know?
My Sultan...
I don't want to bear anyone's guilt.
- But...
- But what, Ayhan Ağa?
If there was a market like you claim...
everyone who sets a stall in that market
has declared war on us.
Mehmet Bey immediately declared war.
I say all this objectively.
I mean, thank God, even Osman Bey's
stalls are in your market.
It means that the people trust him completely.
- He will stand before the people now...
- Who is Osman in front of Sultan Yakup?
Who is Osman? How dare you?
You say that the people stand behind Osman.
If our market doesn't do well,
and people lose trust...
Osman will take advantage of this?
No, I seek Allah's forgiveness.
I fear Allah.
I love Osman Bey...
this would be slander, and
this body would burn in hell.
I am a trader, my sultan.
My mind doesn't understand.
I'm searching for meaning in
what I know and what I see.
I wanted to consult you on
these meanings.
I don't understand these things.
May I come in, my Sultan?
Come in.
There is an infiltration on
the caged tent, my sultan.
What's going on?
Is it Osman?
We'll find out, Hatun.
Gonca.
These are Byzantine dogs.
They are clearly up to something.
Alps, my Alps.
Who did this, Gonca?
These are not our Alps, father.
They are plotting something.
They were going to kill Alaeddin Bey.
They wanted to kill me and
blame you, Yakup Bey.
Veysel was also one of them.
Even if we search, there's an unknown
traitor among us, my Bey.
I swear I will root them out.
- If necessary, I will...
- Mehmet Bey.
The fruitful tree gets exposed to worms.
But it doesn't stop bearing fruit,
isn't it?
We'll go on our way.
Alaeddin Bey.
Despite your young age,
you have incredible foresight.
I prefer to see you in front of
me instead of Osman Bey.
Yakup Bey...
if you see foresight in me...
know that it is from my father Osman Bey.
Even this statement shows
that I am not wrong.
Please, Alaeddin Bey...
be a guest at my table tonight.
YENIŞEHIR
Fatma, my daughter. Did Aysima come?
Have you seen her?
She was making sweetmeat
in the kitchen, mother.
Okay.
- Mother.
- Yes, Orhan.
Let's talk, mother.
- Come first, Aysima has come.
- Enough, mother.
What do I keep telling you?
And you keep saying Aysima.
Enough.
I won't disturb you.
Excuse me.
Aysima, my daughter.
Go and look, Fatma.
Are you happy with yourself?
You offended the girl.
I didn't do that, you did, mother.
Orhan!
Stop.
What do you think you're doing?
You will apologise to Aysima
immediately tomorrow.
Mother, I try not to overstep
my limit or raise my voice...
- But you don't hear me.
- Orhan!
- Come to your senses.
- I'm in my right mind.
From now on...
I will not say another word on this matter.
I will marry Holofira.
And you will show your consent, mother.
Will you go against your mother's
words for Holofira?
Did I raise you like this?
I'm not the one doing this,
you are.
If you go against my words...
and bring Holofira ti this palace...
Yes, mother?
Come on, say it.
Finish your words.
What are you going to do?
What a shame!
This love has blinded your eyes.
I don't know you anymore.
My son...
wouldn't treat his mother and family
in this way.
I don't want to see you.
They gathered here.
Alps!
Look for traces.
We'll find out which way they went.
Come on.
As you command, my Prince
My Bey.
There are boot tracks.
Turkmen boots.
Their numbers are very large.
Those who have infiltrated us
are even more than we imagined.
That's right, my Bey.
They are plotting things in secret.
Like the Mongols...
they attack secretly.
Shall I tell you a secret, son?
The Mongols and Byzantines began
attacking in a hidden manner.
They can no longer face us
as they used to before.
Because we are stronger than them.
Okay, my Bey.
Tell me.
My Bey, we found where
the traces lead to.
Let's go and get that dog.
Listen to me carefully now.
We couldn't do anything about
him following Veysel.
Okay...
they have no choice.
But, father...
We didn't cut off his head because
he said he would manage on his own.
And now he says that he
will lead, father.
He invites the Beys to
take their allegiance.
Speak, father.
Who is Osman?
You will give me permission.
I will level Yenişehir to the ground.
And if you don't give me permission...
I don't care how many men I have,
I will attack that palace, father.
Mehmet!
Listen to me so that there is a
difference between you and Osman.
The time for words is over.
The swords will speak now.
Mehmet!
Go and sit down!
And attack them like a rabid dog.
Mehmet.
Son.
I leave you a position and a throne.
Whoever sits on the throne must know.
If the Sultan draws his sword early...
he will descend.
And if the time has come
to draw the sword...
he does not get his hands dirty.
Kanyumaz.
Who knows about the bannerless
withdrawing their pledge from Osman?
Only Osman knows, my Sultan.
He didn't announce it out of shame.
Good.
Mehmet.
Send news to the Bannerless.
Will they strike Osman?
Not Osman.
They will strike the Turkmen Beys
whom Osman invited.
The route of the Beys is known.
But don't you...
don't you, Mehmet...
don't you dare!
Those Turkmen Beys are my
own flesh and blood.
Not a single Bey or Alp
will suffer any harm.
We'll just destroy trust
which Othman earned.
But we won't kill anyone.
The Beys will think that Osman
called them to kill them.
That's right.
SECRET SITE NEAR KITE
Greetings.
Orhan!
Yes, Orhan.
How did you find me?
We followed the smell of your fear.
And it led to you, Veysel.
The one who sheds the Turks' blood
cannot run or hide!
Osman's dogs!
You've come to your death.
I will bless your blood with my wrath now.
Look here!
Look at this.
While we were looking for one,
both suddenly came out in front of us.
You were here too?
Excellent.
Let's end this now.
Wait, Mongol.
Veysel!
You won't be able to escape
from this corridor.
Tooth for tooth.
Blood for blood.
We'll see, Osman.
You will finally meet Vasilis.
Everyone who knew us is underground.
You must not know us?
You will get to know us now.
Enough!
Soldiers, attack!
Come on then.
I will come back for revenge!
Come on.
Veysel!
Get up. Come on.
Snarl, you dog!
Snarl!
There's no easy death for you.
Get on your feet, you still
have a price to pay!
Since you're so in a hurry to
make me pay the price, Osman...
kill me!
Let's get this over with!
Get up.
With every breath you take,
you will beg for death.
With every breath.
The prey has entered the trap.
Now...
we'll become hunters and cut them off.
But Yakup Bey has strict orders.
None of them will be harmed.
Come on.
Alps!
Defence formation!
Who are they?
The Bannerless!
They pledged allegiance to Osman.
Why are they attacking us then?
Turkmen Beys.
What is this impertinence?
Does Osman Bey know about this?
Osman Bey is the one who sent us.
For the great Turkmen Beys.
He wanted a great reception.
Then the field will belong to the Bannerless.
Osman, how dare you?
How dare you?
The order is Osman Bey's.
Bannerless, strike with your swords!
Allah is the Greatest!
Look at me, you masked devil.
Every time I see your face,
I remember your betrayal.
Don't test my patience, come on.
Be grateful you aren't dead, Boran.
Come on!
Boran, stop.
He will live for now.
My Bey, if this dog lives,
what is the difference?
Boran!
He won't die now.
We won't kill him for revenge,
we'll kill him for Allah's sake.
We will keep the promise we made.
We have to take Alaeddin.
Orhan.
My Bey.
Take this dog to the place of exchange.
Take your brother and come.
As you command, my Bey.
Get up!
Come on!
Bayındır.
My Bey.
Go with them too.
As you command, my Bey.
Peace be upon you, Osman Bey.
Peace be upon you, Dervish Efendi.
It is Allah's way...
I was coming to you and
found you on my way.
You host us every time.
Please come with us to Yenişehir.
And sit at our table.
And the Beys will come too.
Let's talk a little bit.
Of course.
I had something to say...
I'll say it when we arrive, then.
Thank you.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
Give him a horse.
Sure, my Bey.
I will wipe out those who ambush my Beys.
Bannerless ones!
Retreat!
Allah is the Greatest!
- Yakup Bey.
- Are you okay, Beys?
Fine, Mr. Jacob
Praise be to Allah.
You caught up at the right time.
If you hadn't come...
they almost broke our defence.
Praise be to Allah.
Weren't those dogs the Bannerless ones?
They were.
Didn't they pledge allegiance to Osman?
They did.
Well, what Osman Bey get
out of this, Sultan Yakup?
Isn't it obvious?
Can't you see?
Osman wants to become the leader.
He plots many tricks.
He wants to eliminate everyone
who stands before him.
The evidence is clear, Beys,
don't you see?
Greed is enough to make Osman
plot numerous games
We'll make him stop.
We will take revenge for this.
We will hold him accountable for this.
We will.
Osman Bey and his Alps
found Veysel, my Sultan.
Good.
And now, my Beys.
I'll show you the truth.
We will go to Yenişehir.
We will learn the truth
from the Osman's Alp.
We will put an end to Osman's games.
Come on.
Have a good day.
Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
I want to talk to you, Holofira.
I'm listening.
You think I don't like you, don't you?
It's obvious.
I like you, my daughter.
My son loves you, why wouldn't I?
If Orhan weren't a Bey...
we'd be talking about your
wedding now.
But he is a Bey.
It is his destiny to pursue
his father's dream.
If you get married, you will
become the Bey's wife.
You will show the way for all the women.
Look at these people you don't know.
Do you think you'll be able to lead them?
Let's say you can.
Do you think they will accept a
lady who is not of their religion?
Is that the problem?
Is it because I'm a Christian?
This is not the only problem, my daughter.
The problem is that you do not know us.
You do not know our customs and traditions.
You know about me and Bala, right?
I married a Bey who
was already married.
Just to give birth to a child, an heir.
The day came when we gave up on our
lives and our dreams for this dream.
We were content with our fate.
This is the test.
Let's say you didn't give birth
to a child for Orhan...
could you make the sacrifice Bala made...
and consent to Orhan having a second wife?
For Orhan and the Beylik...
for this dream we believe in...
for the sake of all this, are
you willing to risk everything...
and sacrifice everything
when the time comes?
I... this...
I don't hate you, Holofira.
But I don't think about today,
I think about tomorrow.
Go from here.
Don't let Orhan become an enemy to
his mother and father for this reason.
You will understand me in the future,
my daughter.
My lady, are you okay?
You were right, Andra.
I have no future with Orhan.
Come on.
You treacherous dog, come on!
Get up!
Come on, walk, dog!
Walk!
Wait and see, come on!
You'll be held accountable for
everything you've done, come on!
Come on, walk!
You will not die easily.
Wait and see, walk!
Treacherous dog!
Get up! Get up!
Come on!
Mehmet Bey.
I brought the traitor whom you couldn't hold.
Release my brother.
Orhan!
Alps!
Take Veysel.
Stop right there.
We'll make him talk first.
Alps!
Bring Alaeddin.
Stop.
Oh, my son.
Praise be to Allah.
- I'm fine.
- Praise be to Allah.
Brother.
Let me look.
You're fine, aren't you?
He is fine.
Sister.
Praise be to Allah.
Speak, Veysel.
Speak, whose dog are you?
Who helped you flee the market?
Why don't you ask Vasilis?
Maybe he will speak then.
Isn't it, Vasilis?
How many names do you have?
How many faces do you have, dog?
I have many names.
Which name do you want me to use?
You are a pawn, Vasilis!
You are the tongs held by
those scared of the fire.
I am ancient Rome.
Vasilis, come on, tell me.
Who is your master?
Ancient Rome...
will come back someday.
And you won't live to see this.
I will kill you all.
- You're going to kill us all?
- Yes.
You will not die easily!
YENIŞEHIR
You honoured us, Dervish Efendi.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
We were very tired.
We suffered a lot.
We got very angry.
Let's catch our breath.
What did our ancestors say?
He who gets up in anger
always suffers losses.
Excuse me, Dervish Efendi...
But Hazret Umar (RA)
was known for his anger.
The infidels always received
their share of his wrath.
Don't we always need the same anger?
If it can be like the anger of Hazret Omar (RA)
and the companions.
Not for our desires.
But for the sake of Allah's pleasure.
Anger with no arrogance nor selfishness.
Since we mentioned it, let me tell you.
Let's talk about the companions.
Do tell us.
Vasilis, look.
Look to my eyes.
Let me tell you a secret.
Not only to the Byzantium...
we will march towards the furthest
borders of Rome.
We'll even surpass it.
There they will speak our language.
And they will live according
to our religion there.
The call to prayer will not stop
in the heart of the crusaders.
Orhan.
You are dreaming.
I will survive from here.
You'll get out of here, is it?
I will be your executioner.
Lift him up.
You baseborn dog!
I know how to make him talk.
Alps, take him to the cage tent.
He will not be unattended until Yakup Bey comes.
That's right.
But be careful.
Don't let them snatch him away
from you again, Mehmet Bey.
Mind your business, Orhan!
Orhan, let's go, son.
Let's go, mother.
Come on, Alaeddin.
- Come on, sister.
- Fatma, come on.
I will wait for you at the market crossroads.
Okay.
In the golden era, on the battlefield...
the Messenger of Allah (PBUH)
pointed to one of the infidels...
and asked: "Oh Ali, do you want
to fight this infidel?"
Hazret Ali (RA) said: "Permit me...
with Allah's grace and will...
I will save the Muslims from
the evil of this infidel."
The Messenger of Allah said: "Oh Ali...
I entrust you to the safety of Allah who
created the earth and the heavens."
Hazret Ali (RA) went out to the
field and confronted the infidel.
He invited the infidel to bring faith first.
When the infidel rejected the invitation,
the fight started.
After a short while, Hazret Ali (RA) made him
fall to the ground and knelt on his chest.
He put his sword to his neck.
He invited him to bring faith again.
When the infidel understood
that he wouldn't survive this...
he spat in the face of Hazret Ali (RA).
Hazret Ali (RA) sheathed his sword
and then rose to his feet.
The man was surprised.
He said: "Oh Ali, I spat in your
face to make you angry."
"So that you kill me immediately
and I may be free."
"But you sheathed your sword and got up."
"I don't understand your reason for this."
Hazret Ali (RA) was silent first.
Then he looked at his face and said:
"Oh infidel."
"I didn't kill you right away, I waited."
"I invited you to bring faith."
"This is for the sake of Islam
and for the sake of Allah."
"Then when you spat in my face...
I took it badly."
"When this happened I was afraid
I would kill you for myself, not for Allah...
so I put my sword in its sheath."
After this, the man said:
"Since you have such good intentions...
such kindness and benevolence,
your religion is the religion of truth."
"Show me how to believe and be a Muslim."
Hazret Ali (RA) told him to say the testimony.
He said the testimony and became a Muslim.
He even served Hazret Ali (RA) until his death.
Now you will say I told
you something again...
but why this?
The Messenger of Allah (PBUH) says:
"Actions are according to intentions."
If your intention is the pleasure of Allah...
many doors of goodness will open
after your action.
Who knows, maybe you be the reason
to guide many infidels.
In Sha Allah.
I told you this...
so that you know that...
your mercy and anger has value
when it is for the sake of Allah...
and live according to this.
Bless your tongue.
May you live long. Bless your words.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in.
Peace be upon you.
My Bey, there is an important matter.
No, please be seated.
- My Bey.
- Tell me.
They attacked the Beys.
Who attacked them?
Who?
The Bannerless, my Bey.
What?
Why would the Bannerless
do something like this?
Tell me, what happened?
They said your name, my Bey.
They attacked them in the
name of Osman Bey.
What?
Yakup Bey caught up with them later.
Yakup?
Yakup, huh?
As long as there is such a Bey...
what's the need for an enemy?
He will make me look like
a traitor to the Beys.
So this is his game.
Now, will they go to the market, my Bey?
No.
They will come to us.
Listen to me carefully.
I trust you now, deceitful Hatun.
Schoolboy?
Welcome, deceitful Hatun.
Why did you call me here?
Couldn't you say what you
wanted in the market?
We haven't raced in a long time.
I thought you missed it.
What is it? Are you afraid?
Afraid of you?
I will defeat you this time, schoolboy,
just saying.
Okay.
And you should know that
I will win this race.
And I'm going to ask something of you.
Allah Allah, what will you ask for?
You'll find out when I win.
We'll go to that hill and come back.
Whoever gets there first wins.
Okay.
Come on then.
Let's go.
Come on, deceitful Hatun.
Come on.
- Come on!
Now the Beys will come
towards us with slander.
They will be angry.
But we will remain calm.
Calmness always defeats anger, my Bey.
As long as they don't cross their limits.
They will do that too.
We will show tolerance.
None of you will draw your
sword without my order.
Şamil.
The wind does not calm
down in these lands.
Tell me, how are things in Shusha?
All is well in Shusha, my Bey.
I brought you greetings from Shusha.
And may peace be upon you.
We convey our greetings to Shusha too.
Sure, my Bey.
We'll see.
Will peace come to us from the
Beys or misfortunes?
We'll see.
Come on, come on.
Come on!
- Come on!
Well, I won this race, deceitful Hatun.
This is punishment for that training, isn't it?
You couldn't bear that defeat, schoolboy.
I don't know.
Maybe I didn't want to win.
But today is not the case.
I needed to beat you today.
Say, what will you ask?
You're wondering, aren't you?
Look, if you play around again,
I swear I'll go.
You can't go anywhere.
Since I won the race,
what I say will happen.
Is this flower yours?
Why is it with you?
Answer my question first.
I'm going.
Gonca.
Don't go.
If you know, why do you ask, schoolboy?
I want to be sure.
Actually, you know.
But you don't trust me, schoolboy.
I always listened to my mind.
That's why I always falter.
But...
it's such a matter...
I don't know how to say it.
Gonca.
Since the first day I saw you...
my heart screams your name such...
forget my mind, I don't listen to anyone.
I can't even hear myself, Gonca.
I've been wanting to tell you
something for a while.
I like you, deceitful Hatun.
You called me, Malhun Hatun.
Come, my daughter, come.
My son has something to tell you.
Orhan Bey.
Come here a moment.
Come on, son.
Forgive me for yesterday,
Aysima Hatun.
Holofira.
I always see you upset.
This does not suit you.
Your beautiful eyes should always be happy.
Orhan, don't you dare.
Mother, let me go!
I said, don't you dare, Orhan.
I don't know how to say fancy words.
I...
I want to marry you, Holofira.
Let me go.
I said, don't you dare.
My daughter, Aysima.
Tell your father, it's time to
get to know each other.
I'll tell him, Malhun Hatun.
Now, with your permission.
The stall is unattended.
Permission is yours, my daughter, you may go.
This is very sudden, Mehmet Bey.
If you allow, I want to think about it.
Of course.
But accept my gift.
Then...
I expect to hear from you,
beautiful Holofira.
I'll show you beauty now.
Orhan!
Enough, Orhan!
Don't interfere, mother!
Orhan, I'm talking to you.
You will disgrace us in front of the people.
You are a Bey, come to your senses.
Don't you see Holofira is going her way?
Don't you understand that
Holofira's way is my way, mother?
Not now, Orhan.
YENIŞEHIR
Welcome, Beys.
We were not welcome, Osman Bey.
You tried to make my Beys
bait for the thieves.
And when you failed,
you receive us armed?
Whoever comes to the yard like this,
is received in this way, Yakup Bey.
We thought you were in a
sleep of negligence, Yakup Bey.
We held our anger because
they deceived you.
But I see that you are blind to
what you do not want to see...
and deaf to what you don't want to hear.
Let's say I'm blind...
are my Beys blind too?
They all saw the truth
and they all heard it.
You ambushed the Beys.
We wear armour and hold a shield...
but this does not protect us
from being slandered.
We have completed our
preparations against the enemy.
But the enemy amongst us...
no precaution works against them.
Good.
At least you know yourself.
The Beys trusted you
and took to the road.
Look at this situation you got them into.
I know myself very well.
But I know you too, Yakup Bey.
Beys, you tell me...
didn't any of you come forward and say
Osman Bey wouldn't do this?
Huh? Didn't anyone say this?
You fall into doubt.
Your mind is confused.
But don't worry.
I will remove all these doubts.
Alps!
Close the doors.
I don't know what to do, Andra.
We must go immediately!
Walk!
What are you doing, Orhan?
You will think about it, huh?
- Yes, I will think about it!
- Move away!
- Leave me!
- Come on, walk!
What's happening there?
- Let's go!
- Leave me!
I said leave me!
Leave me!
Get on, come on.
Orhan?
I won't listen to any of you
anymore, come on!
What is this boy doing?
- Mother.
- He's taking Holofira!
Orhan!
Orhan, stop!
It's over now!
I won't listen to any of you!
You shouldn't have done this, Orhan!
Alps, to the horses!
Orhan!
We will stop you, Orhan!
Mother.
- Orhan!
- Mother!
Orhan!
What have you done, son?
What have you done?
Mehmet does not have good intentions.
Come on, go after them!
Oh Allah.
Oh Allah, protect my son.
Come on, come on!
Come on!
You set up a big game, Yakup Bey.
But everyone has a game.
Until the sword is placed on the neck.
The trouble you're in will become
bigger than before, Osman Bey.
While your enemy is one...
don't make it become ten, Osman Bey.
Karesi Bey.
Do you dare to have
me as your enemy?
What is the meaning of closing
the doors, Osman Bey?
We will set up the table.
And we will eat.
We will talk about everything
we need to talk about.
Even if we have uninvited guests among us.
Today the matter will end here.
My Alps went to fetch the Bannerless.
Let them come.
Then we will see who
they took the order from.
From Yakup Bey?
Or from Osman Bey?
You will pay very dearly
for this insolence, Osman.
You will see what it means
to capture the Sultan.
Of course there will be a price.
Let the bannerless come.
Then we will see what the price is.
We will see...
who is a Bey...
and who is the Sultan.
Visit turkision.com for more!